const levelListData = {
  level1: [
    { question: 'あ', answer: 'a' },
    { question: 'い', answer: 'i' },
    { question: 'う', answer: 'u' },
    { question: 'え', answer: 'e' },
    { question: 'お', answer: 'o' }
  ],
  level2: [
    { question: 'か', answer: 'ka' },
    { question: 'き', answer: 'ki' },
    { question: 'く', answer: 'ku' },
    { question: 'け', answer: 'ke' },
    { question: 'こ', answer: 'ko' }
  ],
  level3: [
    { question: 'さ', answer: 'sa' },
    { question: 'し', answer: 'shi' },
    { question: 'す', answer: 'su' },
    { question: 'せ', answer: 'se' },
    { question: 'そ', answer: 'so' }
  ],
  checkpoint1: [
    { question: 'あお', answer: 'blue' },
    { question: 'いいえ', answer: 'no' },
    { question: 'うえ', answer: 'up' },
    { question: 'えき', answer: 'station' },
    { question: 'おおきい', answer: 'big' },
    { question: 'かみ', answer: 'paper' },
    { question: 'きせき', answer: 'magic'},
    { question: 'くつ', answer: 'shoe' },
    { question: 'けいかく', answer: 'plan' },
    { question: 'こえ', answer: 'voice' },
    { question: 'さき', answer: 'ahead' },
    { question: 'しお', answer: 'salt' },
    { question: 'すき', answer: 'love' },
    { question: 'せき', answer: 'chair' },
    { question: 'そこ', answer: 'there' },
  ],
  level4: [
    { question: 'た', answer: 'ta' },
    { question: 'ち', answer: 'chi' },
    { question: 'つ', answer: 'tsu' },
    { question: 'て', answer: 'te' },
    { question: 'と', answer: 'to' }
  ],
  level5: [
    { question: 'な', answer: 'na' },
    { question: 'に', answer: 'ni' },
    { question: 'ぬ', answer: 'nu' },
    { question: 'ね', answer: 'ne' },
    { question: 'の', answer: 'no' }
  ],
  level6: [
    { question: 'は', answer: 'ha' },
    { question: 'ひ', answer: 'hi' },
    { question: 'ふ', answer: 'fu' },
    { question: 'へ', answer: 'he' },
    { question: 'ほ', answer: 'ho' }
  ],
  checkpoint2: [
    { question: 'たかい', answer: 'high' },
    { question: 'ちいさい', answer: 'small' },
    { question: 'つくえ', answer: 'desk' },
    { question: 'てつ', answer: 'iron' },
    { question: 'とし', answer: 'year' },
    { question: 'なつ', answer: 'summer' },
    { question: 'にく', answer: 'meat' },
    { question: 'ぬすむ', answer: 'steal' },
    { question: 'ねこ', answer: 'cat' },
    { question: 'のむ', answer: 'drink' },
    { question: 'はな', answer: 'flower' },
    { question: 'ひと', answer: 'people' },
    { question: 'ふく', answer: 'cloth' },
    { question: 'へいわ', answer: 'peace' },
    { question: 'ほし', answer: 'star' },
  ],
  level7: [
    { question: 'ま', answer: 'ma' },
    { question: 'み', answer: 'mi' },
    { question: 'む', answer: 'mu' },
    { question: 'め', answer: 'me' },
    { question: 'も', answer: 'mo' }
  ],
  level8: [
    { question: 'ら', answer: 'ra' },
    { question: 'り', answer: 'ri' },
    { question: 'る', answer: 'ru' },
    { question: 'れ', answer: 're' },
    { question: 'ろ', answer: 'ro' }
  ],
  level9: [
    { question: 'わ', answer: 'wa' },
    { question: 'を', answer: 'wo' },
    { question: 'ん', answer: 'n' },
    { question: 'や', answer: 'ya' },
    { question: 'ゆ', answer: 'yu' },
    { question: 'よ', answer: 'yo' }
  ],
  checkpoint3: [
    { question: 'まんが', answer: 'comic' },
    { question: 'みみ', answer: 'ear' },
    { question: 'むら', answer: 'village' },
    { question: 'めがね', answer: 'glasses' },
    { question: 'もり', answer: 'forest' },
    { question: 'らめん', answer: 'ramen' },
    { question: 'りす', answer: 'squirrel' },
    { question: 'るす', answer: 'absence' },
    { question: 'れきし', answer: 'history' },
    { question: 'ろく', answer: 'six' },
    { question: 'わかる', answer: 'understand' },
    { question: 'やま', answer: 'mountain' },
    { question: 'ゆき', answer: 'snow' },
    { question: 'よる', answer: 'night' },
  ]
}